stoneberry.com 2012-03-11

# Security and Privacy

    Our Commitment to Privacy

    Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

    How Stoneberry Collects Your Information

    Stoneberry™ and its parent company B.A.Mason Inc.® value and respect your privacy. We collect information about you through our websites and catalog orders in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate our products, services, and promotions to you. The information we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address, and phone number. We also collect information that you submit about other people. For example, if you ship an order to a recipient other than yourself, we collect the recipient's name and address.

    How Stoneberry Uses Your Information

    Stoneberry may use your information to complete your orders, contact you regarding your order, or provide customer service. Stoneberry may also use your information to send you promotional offers from Stoneberry, including our printed catalogs or promotional emails, if you provided your email address to us. 

    From time to time, we may share information we have collected among our other divisions and, under certain circumstances, with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service. 

    You may request that we not share this information with our other divisions and third parties or opt out of receiving promotional messages from Stoneberry by calling us toll-free at 1-800-704-5480, or submitting your request, along with your mailing address, in writing to us at Stoneberry, 1356 Williams Street, Chippewa Falls, WI 54729. Stoneberry will not use your information in ways other than those described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out.

    How You Can Access or Correct Your Information

    You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us by phone at 1-800-704-5480 or by writing to us at Stoneberry, 1356 Williams Street, Chippewa Falls, WI 54729. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

    Customer Review Postings

    Stoneberry allows customer reviews of products using PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions). When you submit a product review, you will be subject to PowerReviews' terms of use and privacy policies. The reviews you submit may be posted on both the PowerReviews site ([http://www.buzzillions.com](http://www.buzzillions.com/)) and our site.

    Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

        Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. Therefore, we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. No part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13 years of age.

    Our Commitment to Security

        Stoneberry uses VeriSign, which offers state-of-the-art, dependable security infrastructure and is the most trusted and recognized security brand on the web. VeriSign ensures that each purchase is backed by the most reliable, secure operations infrastructure, with comprehensive security, trust, and authentication practices. Also, our servers use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) advanced encryption. All credit card transactions are secured by 256-bit encryption. As an added measure of protection, in the unlikely event of credit card fraud, there is still no risk to you. The Fair Credit Act states that your credit card company can hold you liable for a maximum of $50.00 in fraudulent charges. Stoneberry will reimburse you for any charges up to the $50.00 maximum your credit card company can charge you if those charges result from an order placed on our secure server. You can enjoy shopping worry free at Stoneberry.

    Identity Theft Prevention

    Stoneberry maintains a Red Flag Program for Identity Theft Protection to help prevent fraud and identity theft. The risk to our customers, employees and business partners from data loss and identity theft is of significant concern. All of our employees and business partners share in the responsibility of reducing this risk and protecting applicable information for which they have access or custodianship.

        The purpose of the program is to detect, prevent and mitigate identity theft in connection with the opening of a covered account or an existing covered account and to provide for continued administration of the Program in compliance with Part 681 of Title 16 of the Code of Federal Regulations implementing Sections 114 and 315 of the Fair and Accurate Credit Transactions Act (FACTA) of 2003. For further information on “Red Flag” requirements go to <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/business/idtheft/bus23.shtm>

    Changes to this Privacy Policy Statement

    If our policies change at some point of time, we will post the changes on the Privacy Notice page of our website. From time to time, you should check this page for more information on how we use the data we collect. Should you have questions about our privacy or security practices, please contact us by emailing [service@stoneberry.com](mailto:service@stoneberry.com) or calling toll-free 1-800-704-5480.

    Other Legal Information

    **Product Information** - The products displayed at this Site are available while supplies last. The prices displayed at this Site are quoted in U.S. dollars. 

          **Links To Other Web Sites And Services** - This Site may contain links to outside services or resources that Stoneberry does not control. If you have an issue with a linked site that you are unable to resolve directly with them, please let us know. 

          **Terms Of Use** - We welcome you to the Stoneberry website. The rules that apply to your use of our Site are set forth in on this webpage. By using our Site you are agreeing to those rules. We reserve the right to change the rules from time to time. Your ongoing use of the Site means that you agree to the rules as changed.

    **Property Rights** - The entire site as a whole is protected by copyright and trade dress laws. All rights, ownership and interest in are owned by Stoneberry and its parent companies. All identified trademarks appearing at the site are trademarks of Stoneberry and its parent company and all affiliated trademarks of other companies are used with permission. Excepting trademarks and brand names of third parties for merchandise depicted on the Site, or as otherwise noted, all images, materials, designs, photographs, illustrations, icons, videos and other materials that are part of this Site are copyrights, trademarks, trade dress and/or other intellectual properties owned, controlled or licensed by Stoneberry and its parent company. Our Site as a whole, and its contents, are intended solely for personal, non-commercial use by Site users. It is permissible to download or copy contents and other materials subject to downloaded capability displayed on the Site for personal use only. No right, title or interest in any downloaded images or materials or software is transferred to you as a result of any personal copying or downloading. As a Site user, you may not reproduce (except for personal use as noted above), publish, transmit, distribute, display, modify, create derivative works from, sell or participate in any sale of, or otherwise utilize in any way, in whole or in part, any of the Contents, the Site, or any related software without the express written permission of Stoneberry.
